launch the APP and enter the Login page.
If you have an account, you can log in directly.
If not, you can click on
register to sign up. Now, I will focus on our search feature.
Not familiar with the search syntex format?
No worries.
Click on the circular icon. Now let's have a try.
As you can see, we have successfully found the desired results.
Now let's start test out the filter function.
Our filters supports a precise range of selection, various sorting options,
and also utilize the GPS feature to filter nearby restaurants.
We have integrated very user friendly operations.
You can also choose reset to start over.
But clicking on a filtered restaurant, we can feel detailed restaurant information and read the comments below.
You can also leave a comment on this page by clicking on the statistic button.
Users enter the data analysis interface, here we have four graphs.
Next, let's move to the P2P section.
Here, you can search for a friend's account in the search box
or directly select previous chat histories to start a conversation.
Let's chat!  Now, let's switch to another phone account
We have successfully received the message.
Now, looking at the sidebar, from top to button, we have the location displayed by
GPS, a user profile, pictures, and an editable user name.
Next, let's explore the egg's comment history.
We can see our newly added comment here, you can click logout to sign out.
We implement a simulator to load three kinds of simulation data
from file based every time seconds
including surge key words, written data and PTP messages.
The app will automatically update the database and visualize the results.
That's all. Thank you.